{
    "deck": "spanish_words",
    "description": "Top 100 most common Spanish words",
    "question_header": "spanish",
    "answer_header": "english",
    "questions": {
        "question_number_0": {
            "question": "est\u00e1",
            "answer": "this",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_1": {
            "question": "que",
            "answer": "that",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_2": {
            "question": "de",
            "answer": "of",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_3": {
            "question": "no",
            "answer": "No",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_4": {
            "question": "a",
            "answer": "a",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_5": {
            "question": "la",
            "answer": "the",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_6": {
            "question": "el",
            "answer": "the",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_7": {
            "question": "es",
            "answer": "it is",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_8": {
            "question": "y",
            "answer": "Y",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_9": {
            "question": "en",
            "answer": "in",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_10": {
            "question": "lo",
            "answer": "it",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_11": {
            "question": "un",
            "answer": "a",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_12": {
            "question": "por",
            "answer": "by",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_13": {
            "question": "qu\u00e9",
            "answer": "what",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_14": {
            "question": "me",
            "answer": "I",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_15": {
            "question": "una",
            "answer": "a",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_16": {
            "question": "te",
            "answer": "tea",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_17": {
            "question": "los",
            "answer": "the",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_18": {
            "question": "se",
            "answer": "I know",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_19": {
            "question": "con",
            "answer": "with",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_20": {
            "question": "para",
            "answer": "for",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_21": {
            "question": "mi",
            "answer": "me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_22": {
            "question": "si",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_23": {
            "question": "bien",
            "answer": "right",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_24": {
            "question": "pero",
            "answer": "but",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_25": {
            "question": "yo",
            "answer": "me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_26": {
            "question": "eso",
            "answer": "it's",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_27": {
            "question": "las",
            "answer": "the",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_28": {
            "question": "s\u00ed",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_29": {
            "question": "su",
            "answer": "its",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_30": {
            "question": "tu",
            "answer": "your",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_31": {
            "question": "aqu\u00ed",
            "answer": "here",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_32": {
            "question": "del",
            "answer": "of",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_33": {
            "question": "al",
            "answer": "to the",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_34": {
            "question": "como",
            "answer": "What",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_35": {
            "question": "le",
            "answer": "you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_36": {
            "question": "m\u00e1s",
            "answer": "plus",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_37": {
            "question": "esto",
            "answer": "this",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_38": {
            "question": "ya",
            "answer": "Already",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_39": {
            "question": "todo",
            "answer": "all",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_40": {
            "question": "esta",
            "answer": "is",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_41": {
            "question": "vamos",
            "answer": "we go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_42": {
            "question": "muy",
            "answer": "very",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_43": {
            "question": "hay",
            "answer": "there are",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_44": {
            "question": "ahora",
            "answer": "now",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_45": {
            "question": "algo",
            "answer": "something",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_46": {
            "question": "estoy",
            "answer": "am",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_47": {
            "question": "tengo",
            "answer": "I've got",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_48": {
            "question": "nos",
            "answer": "us",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_49": {
            "question": "t\u00fa",
            "answer": "your",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_50": {
            "question": "nada",
            "answer": "any",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_51": {
            "question": "cuando",
            "answer": "when",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_52": {
            "question": "ha",
            "answer": "he has",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_53": {
            "question": "este",
            "answer": "East",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_54": {
            "question": "s\u00e9",
            "answer": "HE",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_55": {
            "question": "est\u00e1s",
            "answer": "are",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_56": {
            "question": "as\u00ed",
            "answer": "So",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_57": {
            "question": "puedo",
            "answer": "Can I",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_58": {
            "question": "c\u00f3mo",
            "answer": "What",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_59": {
            "question": "quiero",
            "answer": "I want",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_60": {
            "question": "s\u00f3lo",
            "answer": "single",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_61": {
            "question": "soy",
            "answer": "am",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_62": {
            "question": "tiene",
            "answer": "have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_63": {
            "question": "gracias",
            "answer": "Thank you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_64": {
            "question": "o",
            "answer": "either",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_65": {
            "question": "\u00e9l",
            "answer": "the",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_66": {
            "question": "bueno",
            "answer": "Okay",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_67": {
            "question": "fue",
            "answer": "it was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_68": {
            "question": "ser",
            "answer": "be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_69": {
            "question": "hacer",
            "answer": "do",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_70": {
            "question": "son",
            "answer": "are",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_71": {
            "question": "todos",
            "answer": "everybody",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_72": {
            "question": "era",
            "answer": "it was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_73": {
            "question": "eres",
            "answer": "are",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_74": {
            "question": "vez",
            "answer": "time",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_75": {
            "question": "tienes",
            "answer": "you have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_76": {
            "question": "creo",
            "answer": "I think",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_77": {
            "question": "ella",
            "answer": "she",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_78": {
            "question": "he",
            "answer": "He",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_79": {
            "question": "ese",
            "answer": "that",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_80": {
            "question": "voy",
            "answer": "I go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_81": {
            "question": "puede",
            "answer": "can",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_82": {
            "question": "sabes",
            "answer": "you know",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_83": {
            "question": "hola",
            "answer": "hello",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_84": {
            "question": "sus",
            "answer": "their",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_85": {
            "question": "porque",
            "answer": "because",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_86": {
            "question": "dios",
            "answer": "god",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_87": {
            "question": "qui\u00e9n",
            "answer": "who",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_88": {
            "question": "nunca",
            "answer": "never",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_89": {
            "question": "d\u00f3nde",
            "answer": "where",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_90": {
            "question": "quieres",
            "answer": "you want",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_91": {
            "question": "casa",
            "answer": "House",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_92": {
            "question": "favor",
            "answer": "favour",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_93": {
            "question": "esa",
            "answer": "this",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_94": {
            "question": "dos",
            "answer": "two",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_95": {
            "question": "tan",
            "answer": "so",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_96": {
            "question": "se\u00f1or",
            "answer": "mister",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_97": {
            "question": "tiempo",
            "answer": "weather",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_98": {
            "question": "verdad",
            "answer": "TRUE",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_99": {
            "question": "estaba",
            "answer": "I was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_100": {
            "question": "mejor",
            "answer": "better",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_101": {
            "question": "est\u00e1n",
            "answer": "is it so",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_102": {
            "question": "va",
            "answer": "goes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_103": {
            "question": "hombre",
            "answer": "men",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_104": {
            "question": "usted",
            "answer": "you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_105": {
            "question": "mucho",
            "answer": "much",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_106": {
            "question": "hace",
            "answer": "does",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_107": {
            "question": "entonces",
            "answer": "then",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_108": {
            "question": "siento",
            "answer": "I feel",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_109": {
            "question": "tenemos",
            "answer": "we have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_110": {
            "question": "puedes",
            "answer": "you may",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_111": {
            "question": "ah\u00ed",
            "answer": "there",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_112": {
            "question": "ti",
            "answer": "you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_113": {
            "question": "vida",
            "answer": "life",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_114": {
            "question": "ver",
            "answer": "watch",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_115": {
            "question": "alguien",
            "answer": "someone",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_116": {
            "question": "sr",
            "answer": "Mr",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_117": {
            "question": "hasta",
            "answer": "until",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_118": {
            "question": "sin",
            "answer": "without",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_119": {
            "question": "m\u00ed",
            "answer": "my",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_120": {
            "question": "solo",
            "answer": "only",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_121": {
            "question": "a\u00f1os",
            "answer": "years",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_122": {
            "question": "sobre",
            "answer": "on",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_123": {
            "question": "decir",
            "answer": "tell",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_124": {
            "question": "uno",
            "answer": "one",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_125": {
            "question": "siempre",
            "answer": "forever",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_126": {
            "question": "oh",
            "answer": "Oh",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_127": {
            "question": "ir",
            "answer": "to go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_128": {
            "question": "cosas",
            "answer": "stuff",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_129": {
            "question": "tambi\u00e9n",
            "answer": "also",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_130": {
            "question": "antes",
            "answer": "before",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_131": {
            "question": "has",
            "answer": "you have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_132": {
            "question": "ni",
            "answer": "neither",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_133": {
            "question": "mis",
            "answer": "my",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_134": {
            "question": "d\u00eda",
            "answer": "day",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_135": {
            "question": "estar",
            "answer": "be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_136": {
            "question": "estamos",
            "answer": "we're",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_137": {
            "question": "noche",
            "answer": "night",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_138": {
            "question": "nadie",
            "answer": "no one",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_139": {
            "question": "otra",
            "answer": "other",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_140": {
            "question": "quiere",
            "answer": "wants",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_141": {
            "question": "parece",
            "answer": "It seems",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_142": {
            "question": "nosotros",
            "answer": "us",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_143": {
            "question": "poco",
            "answer": "little bit",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_144": {
            "question": "padre",
            "answer": "dad",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_145": {
            "question": "trabajo",
            "answer": "worked",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_146": {
            "question": "gente",
            "answer": "people",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_147": {
            "question": "mira",
            "answer": "look",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_148": {
            "question": "vas",
            "answer": "you go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_149": {
            "question": "sea",
            "answer": "be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_150": {
            "question": "les",
            "answer": "them",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_151": {
            "question": "donde",
            "answer": "where",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_152": {
            "question": "mismo",
            "answer": "same",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_153": {
            "question": "hecho",
            "answer": "done",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_154": {
            "question": "ellos",
            "answer": "they",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_155": {
            "question": "dijo",
            "answer": "said",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_156": {
            "question": "pasa",
            "answer": "happens",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_157": {
            "question": "dinero",
            "answer": "money",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_158": {
            "question": "hijo",
            "answer": "son",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_159": {
            "question": "tal",
            "answer": "such",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_160": {
            "question": "otro",
            "answer": "other",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_161": {
            "question": "hablar",
            "answer": "speak",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_162": {
            "question": "seguro",
            "answer": "sure",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_163": {
            "question": "claro",
            "answer": "Sure",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_164": {
            "question": "estas",
            "answer": "these",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_165": {
            "question": "lugar",
            "answer": "place",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_166": {
            "question": "mundo",
            "answer": "world",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_167": {
            "question": "amigo",
            "answer": "dude",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_168": {
            "question": "espera",
            "answer": "wait",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_169": {
            "question": "mierda",
            "answer": "shit",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_170": {
            "question": "han",
            "answer": "they have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_171": {
            "question": "tus",
            "answer": "your",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_172": {
            "question": "sabe",
            "answer": "knows",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_173": {
            "question": "despu\u00e9s",
            "answer": "after",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_174": {
            "question": "momento",
            "answer": "moment",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_175": {
            "question": "desde",
            "answer": "since",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_176": {
            "question": "fuera",
            "answer": "outside",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_177": {
            "question": "cosa",
            "answer": "stuff",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_178": {
            "question": "tipo",
            "answer": "Type",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_179": {
            "question": "ma\u00f1ana",
            "answer": "morning",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_180": {
            "question": "podemos",
            "answer": "can",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_181": {
            "question": "dije",
            "answer": "said",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_182": {
            "question": "gran",
            "answer": "great",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_183": {
            "question": "necesito",
            "answer": "needed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_184": {
            "question": "estado",
            "answer": "condition",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_185": {
            "question": "podr\u00eda",
            "answer": "could",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_186": {
            "question": "acuerdo",
            "answer": "agreement",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_187": {
            "question": "pap\u00e1",
            "answer": "father",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_188": {
            "question": "tener",
            "answer": "to have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_189": {
            "question": "dice",
            "answer": "He says",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_190": {
            "question": "m\u00edo",
            "answer": "Own",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_191": {
            "question": "crees",
            "answer": "You believe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_192": {
            "question": "buena",
            "answer": "good",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_193": {
            "question": "gusta",
            "answer": "like",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_194": {
            "question": "nuestro",
            "answer": "our",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_195": {
            "question": "nuevo",
            "answer": "new",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_196": {
            "question": "ser\u00e1",
            "answer": "will be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_197": {
            "question": "haciendo",
            "answer": "making",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_198": {
            "question": "d\u00edas",
            "answer": "days",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_199": {
            "question": "nombre",
            "answer": "Name",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_200": {
            "question": "buen",
            "answer": "good",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_201": {
            "question": "hab\u00eda",
            "answer": "there was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_202": {
            "question": "ven",
            "answer": "come",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_203": {
            "question": "tres",
            "answer": "three",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_204": {
            "question": "menos",
            "answer": "less",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_205": {
            "question": "debe",
            "answer": "must",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_206": {
            "question": "ten\u00eda",
            "answer": "I had",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_207": {
            "question": "mal",
            "answer": "wrong",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_208": {
            "question": "conmigo",
            "answer": "with me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_209": {
            "question": "madre",
            "answer": "mother",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_210": {
            "question": "hoy",
            "answer": "today",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_211": {
            "question": "quien",
            "answer": "who",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_212": {
            "question": "sido",
            "answer": "been",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_213": {
            "question": "mam\u00e1",
            "answer": "breast",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_214": {
            "question": "tienen",
            "answer": "have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_215": {
            "question": "luego",
            "answer": "later",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_216": {
            "question": "todas",
            "answer": "all",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_217": {
            "question": "all\u00ed",
            "answer": "over there",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_218": {
            "question": "toda",
            "answer": "all",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_219": {
            "question": "hora",
            "answer": "hour",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_220": {
            "question": "mujer",
            "answer": "woman",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_221": {
            "question": "visto",
            "answer": "viewed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_222": {
            "question": "haces",
            "answer": "you do",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_223": {
            "question": "importa",
            "answer": "It matters",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_224": {
            "question": "contigo",
            "answer": "with you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_225": {
            "question": "ve",
            "answer": "go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_226": {
            "question": "tarde",
            "answer": "afternoon",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_227": {
            "question": "oye",
            "answer": "hears",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_228": {
            "question": "parte",
            "answer": "part",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_229": {
            "question": "haber",
            "answer": "to have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_230": {
            "question": "hombres",
            "answer": "mens",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_231": {
            "question": "problema",
            "answer": "issue",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_232": {
            "question": "mas",
            "answer": "plus",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_233": {
            "question": "saber",
            "answer": "to know",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_234": {
            "question": "quer\u00eda",
            "answer": "wanted",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_235": {
            "question": "a\u00fan",
            "answer": "even",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_236": {
            "question": "veces",
            "answer": "times",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_237": {
            "question": "nuestra",
            "answer": "our",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_238": {
            "question": "hacerlo",
            "answer": "do it",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_239": {
            "question": "cada",
            "answer": "each",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_240": {
            "question": "hizo",
            "answer": "made",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_241": {
            "question": "veo",
            "answer": "I see",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_242": {
            "question": "tanto",
            "answer": "so much",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_243": {
            "question": "raz\u00f3n",
            "answer": "reason",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_244": {
            "question": "ustedes",
            "answer": "your",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_245": {
            "question": "idea",
            "answer": "idea",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_246": {
            "question": "esos",
            "answer": "those",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_247": {
            "question": "van",
            "answer": "go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_248": {
            "question": "quiz\u00e1",
            "answer": "Maybe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_249": {
            "question": "debo",
            "answer": "I shall",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_250": {
            "question": "alguna",
            "answer": "some",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_251": {
            "question": "cierto",
            "answer": "certain",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_252": {
            "question": "ud",
            "answer": "You",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_253": {
            "question": "muerto",
            "answer": "dead",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_254": {
            "question": "unos",
            "answer": "some",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_255": {
            "question": "estos",
            "answer": "these",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_256": {
            "question": "salir",
            "answer": "leave",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_257": {
            "question": "polic\u00eda",
            "answer": "policeman",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_258": {
            "question": "realmente",
            "answer": "Really",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_259": {
            "question": "demasiado",
            "answer": "too",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_260": {
            "question": "familia",
            "answer": "family",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_261": {
            "question": "pueden",
            "answer": "they can",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_262": {
            "question": "cabeza",
            "answer": "head",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_263": {
            "question": "hemos",
            "answer": "we have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_264": {
            "question": "amigos",
            "answer": "friends",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_265": {
            "question": "chica",
            "answer": "girl",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_266": {
            "question": "cari\u00f1o",
            "answer": "sweetie",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_267": {
            "question": "lado",
            "answer": "side",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_268": {
            "question": "all\u00e1",
            "answer": "there",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_269": {
            "question": "entre",
            "answer": "Come in",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_270": {
            "question": "minutos",
            "answer": "minutes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_271": {
            "question": "digo",
            "answer": "say",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_272": {
            "question": "alg\u00fan",
            "answer": "some",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_273": {
            "question": "serio",
            "answer": "I laughed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_274": {
            "question": "cuidado",
            "answer": "watch out",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_275": {
            "question": "pas\u00f3",
            "answer": "I pass",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_276": {
            "question": "buenas",
            "answer": "good",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_277": {
            "question": "somos",
            "answer": "are",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_278": {
            "question": "amor",
            "answer": "love",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_279": {
            "question": "puerta",
            "answer": "gate",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_280": {
            "question": "ves",
            "answer": "you see",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_281": {
            "question": "vaya",
            "answer": "wow",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_282": {
            "question": "ah",
            "answer": "ah",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_283": {
            "question": "suerte",
            "answer": "luck",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_284": {
            "question": "eh",
            "answer": "Hey",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_285": {
            "question": "r\u00e1pido",
            "answer": "Quick",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_286": {
            "question": "cuenta",
            "answer": "bill",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_287": {
            "question": "quiz\u00e1s",
            "answer": "maybe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_288": {
            "question": "esas",
            "answer": "those",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_289": {
            "question": "pues",
            "answer": "well",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_290": {
            "question": "pasado",
            "answer": "past",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_291": {
            "question": "pens\u00e9",
            "answer": "I thought",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_292": {
            "question": "todav\u00eda",
            "answer": "yet",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_293": {
            "question": "hermano",
            "answer": "brother",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_294": {
            "question": "debes",
            "answer": "you should",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_295": {
            "question": "casi",
            "answer": "almost",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_296": {
            "question": "forma",
            "answer": "form",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_297": {
            "question": "aqui",
            "answer": "here",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_298": {
            "question": "chico",
            "answer": "boy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_299": {
            "question": "ok",
            "answer": "okay",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_300": {
            "question": "dicho",
            "answer": "saying",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_301": {
            "question": "nueva",
            "answer": "new",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_302": {
            "question": "sab\u00eda",
            "answer": "I knew",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_303": {
            "question": "muchas",
            "answer": "many",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_304": {
            "question": "dentro",
            "answer": "within",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_305": {
            "question": "hice",
            "answer": "I did",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_306": {
            "question": "contra",
            "answer": "against",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_307": {
            "question": "auto",
            "answer": "auto",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_308": {
            "question": "camino",
            "answer": "road",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_309": {
            "question": "ayuda",
            "answer": "aid",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_310": {
            "question": "primera",
            "answer": "first",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_311": {
            "question": "hacia",
            "answer": "towards",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_312": {
            "question": "vi",
            "answer": "saw",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_313": {
            "question": "miedo",
            "answer": "fear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_314": {
            "question": "adi\u00f3s",
            "answer": "bye",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_315": {
            "question": "primero",
            "answer": "first",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_316": {
            "question": "deber\u00eda",
            "answer": "should",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_317": {
            "question": "poder",
            "answer": "can",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_318": {
            "question": "ni\u00f1os",
            "answer": "kids",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_319": {
            "question": "ser\u00eda",
            "answer": "would",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_320": {
            "question": "historia",
            "answer": "history",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_321": {
            "question": "hey",
            "answer": "Hey",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_322": {
            "question": "mientras",
            "answer": "while",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_323": {
            "question": "ciudad",
            "answer": "city",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_324": {
            "question": "dijiste",
            "answer": "said",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_325": {
            "question": "espero",
            "answer": "wait",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_326": {
            "question": "cu\u00e1nto",
            "answer": "how many",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_327": {
            "question": "esposa",
            "answer": "wife",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_328": {
            "question": "pronto",
            "answer": "early",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_329": {
            "question": "chicos",
            "answer": "Boys",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_330": {
            "question": "cualquier",
            "answer": "any",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_331": {
            "question": "viejo",
            "answer": "old",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_332": {
            "question": "debemos",
            "answer": "must",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_333": {
            "question": "deja",
            "answer": "let",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_334": {
            "question": "a\u00f1o",
            "answer": "year",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_335": {
            "question": "muerte",
            "answer": "death",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_336": {
            "question": "hablando",
            "answer": "talking",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_337": {
            "question": "manos",
            "answer": "hands",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_338": {
            "question": "da",
            "answer": "gives",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_339": {
            "question": "loco",
            "answer": "crazy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_340": {
            "question": "problemas",
            "answer": "problems",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_341": {
            "question": "mano",
            "answer": "hand",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_342": {
            "question": "guerra",
            "answer": "war",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_343": {
            "question": "semana",
            "answer": "week",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_344": {
            "question": "pasar",
            "answer": "spend",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_345": {
            "question": "vale",
            "answer": "okay",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_346": {
            "question": "cu\u00e1l",
            "answer": "which",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_347": {
            "question": "viene",
            "answer": "comes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_348": {
            "question": "volver",
            "answer": "return",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_349": {
            "question": "toma",
            "answer": "taking",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_350": {
            "question": "caso",
            "answer": "case",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_351": {
            "question": "agua",
            "answer": "Water",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_352": {
            "question": "har\u00e9",
            "answer": "I will do",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_353": {
            "question": "vete",
            "answer": "go away",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_354": {
            "question": "entiendo",
            "answer": "I get it",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_355": {
            "question": "horas",
            "answer": "hours",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_356": {
            "question": "personas",
            "answer": "people",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_357": {
            "question": "capit\u00e1n",
            "answer": "captain",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_358": {
            "question": "adelante",
            "answer": "ahead",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_359": {
            "question": "ni\u00f1o",
            "answer": "little boy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_360": {
            "question": "listo",
            "answer": "clever",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_361": {
            "question": "noches",
            "answer": "nights",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_362": {
            "question": "buenos",
            "answer": "good ones",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_363": {
            "question": "iba",
            "answer": "I was going",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_364": {
            "question": "juntos",
            "answer": "together",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_365": {
            "question": "dame",
            "answer": "give to me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_366": {
            "question": "\u00fanico",
            "answer": "unique",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_367": {
            "question": "d\u00e9jame",
            "answer": "let me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_368": {
            "question": "cerca",
            "answer": "close",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_369": {
            "question": "otros",
            "answer": "others",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_370": {
            "question": "sigue",
            "answer": "follow",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_371": {
            "question": "grande",
            "answer": "great",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_372": {
            "question": "arriba",
            "answer": "up",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_373": {
            "question": "jefe",
            "answer": "boss",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_374": {
            "question": "habla",
            "answer": "speech",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_375": {
            "question": "supongo",
            "answer": "I guess",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_376": {
            "question": "manera",
            "answer": "way",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_377": {
            "question": "quieren",
            "answer": "They want",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_378": {
            "question": "feliz",
            "answer": "happy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_379": {
            "question": "significa",
            "answer": "it means",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_380": {
            "question": "sangre",
            "answer": "blood",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_381": {
            "question": "fin",
            "answer": "finish",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_382": {
            "question": "bajo",
            "answer": "bass",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_383": {
            "question": "llama",
            "answer": "call",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_384": {
            "question": "venir",
            "answer": "to come",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_385": {
            "question": "morir",
            "answer": "To die",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_386": {
            "question": "importante",
            "answer": "important",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_387": {
            "question": "hiciste",
            "answer": "did",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_388": {
            "question": "ojos",
            "answer": "eyes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_389": {
            "question": "escucha",
            "answer": "listen",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_390": {
            "question": "entrar",
            "answer": "get in",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_391": {
            "question": "ning\u00fan",
            "answer": "none",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_392": {
            "question": "coraz\u00f3n",
            "answer": "heart",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_393": {
            "question": "diablos",
            "answer": "Devils",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_394": {
            "question": "necesitamos",
            "answer": "need",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_395": {
            "question": "atr\u00e1s",
            "answer": "behind",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_396": {
            "question": "durante",
            "answer": "during",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_397": {
            "question": "dices",
            "answer": "You say",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_398": {
            "question": "nuestros",
            "answer": "our",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_399": {
            "question": "persona",
            "answer": "person",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_400": {
            "question": "abajo",
            "answer": "down",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_401": {
            "question": "dr",
            "answer": "Dr.",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_402": {
            "question": "hija",
            "answer": "daughter",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_403": {
            "question": "dejar",
            "answer": "let",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_404": {
            "question": "necesita",
            "answer": "needs to",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_405": {
            "question": "llegar",
            "answer": "get",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_406": {
            "question": "hago",
            "answer": "I make",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_407": {
            "question": "se\u00f1ora",
            "answer": "Mrs",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_408": {
            "question": "haya",
            "answer": "is",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_409": {
            "question": "suficiente",
            "answer": "enough",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_410": {
            "question": "doctor",
            "answer": "doctor",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_411": {
            "question": "gustar\u00eda",
            "answer": "would like",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_412": {
            "question": "tierra",
            "answer": "Earth",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_413": {
            "question": "cara",
            "answer": "expensive",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_414": {
            "question": "siquiera",
            "answer": "even",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_415": {
            "question": "genial",
            "answer": "cool",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_416": {
            "question": "cree",
            "answer": "Believe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_417": {
            "question": "supuesto",
            "answer": "supposed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_418": {
            "question": "tomar",
            "answer": "drink",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_419": {
            "question": "equipo",
            "answer": "equipment",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_420": {
            "question": "justo",
            "answer": "just",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_421": {
            "question": "juego",
            "answer": "play",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_422": {
            "question": "ninguna",
            "answer": "none",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_423": {
            "question": "matar",
            "answer": "to kill",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_424": {
            "question": "cinco",
            "answer": "five",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_425": {
            "question": "dicen",
            "answer": "They say",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_426": {
            "question": "amo",
            "answer": "love",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_427": {
            "question": "cu\u00e1ndo",
            "answer": "when",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_428": {
            "question": "peque\u00f1o",
            "answer": "little",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_429": {
            "question": "algunos",
            "answer": "Some",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_430": {
            "question": "conozco",
            "answer": "know",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_431": {
            "question": "clase",
            "answer": "class",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_432": {
            "question": "maldito",
            "answer": "damned",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_433": {
            "question": "unas",
            "answer": "nail",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_434": {
            "question": "muchos",
            "answer": "Many",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_435": {
            "question": "hubiera",
            "answer": "had",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_436": {
            "question": "segundo",
            "answer": "second",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_437": {
            "question": "aunque",
            "answer": "though",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_438": {
            "question": "pueda",
            "answer": "I can",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_439": {
            "question": "dime",
            "answer": "tell me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_440": {
            "question": "igual",
            "answer": "Same",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_441": {
            "question": "comida",
            "answer": "food",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_442": {
            "question": "ay",
            "answer": "Oh",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_443": {
            "question": "cuerpo",
            "answer": "Body",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_444": {
            "question": "encontrar",
            "answer": "find",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_445": {
            "question": "fuerte",
            "answer": "strong",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_446": {
            "question": "vuelta",
            "answer": "lap",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_447": {
            "question": "venga",
            "answer": "come on",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_448": {
            "question": "creer",
            "answer": "believe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_449": {
            "question": "realidad",
            "answer": "reality",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_450": {
            "question": "saben",
            "answer": "They know",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_451": {
            "question": "puta",
            "answer": "bitch",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_452": {
            "question": "deber\u00edas",
            "answer": "you should",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_453": {
            "question": "pregunta",
            "answer": "Question",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_454": {
            "question": "fui",
            "answer": "I was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_455": {
            "question": "cuatro",
            "answer": "four",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_456": {
            "question": "sra",
            "answer": "Mrs",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_457": {
            "question": "primer",
            "answer": "first",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_458": {
            "question": "trabajar",
            "answer": "to work",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_459": {
            "question": "e",
            "answer": "and",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_460": {
            "question": "hagas",
            "answer": "you do",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_461": {
            "question": "alto",
            "answer": "tall",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_462": {
            "question": "maldita",
            "answer": "damn",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_463": {
            "question": "comer",
            "answer": "to eat",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_464": {
            "question": "n\u00famero",
            "answer": "number",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_465": {
            "question": "dar",
            "answer": "to give",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_466": {
            "question": "necesitas",
            "answer": "you need",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_467": {
            "question": "oportunidad",
            "answer": "chance",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_468": {
            "question": "punto",
            "answer": "point",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_469": {
            "question": "misma",
            "answer": "same",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_470": {
            "question": "\u00faltima",
            "answer": "last",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_471": {
            "question": "afuera",
            "answer": "outside",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_472": {
            "question": "mujeres",
            "answer": "women",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_473": {
            "question": "pensar",
            "answer": "to think",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_474": {
            "question": "fueron",
            "answer": "were",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_475": {
            "question": "dif\u00edcil",
            "answer": "hard",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_476": {
            "question": "vivir",
            "answer": "to live",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_477": {
            "question": "paso",
            "answer": "step",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_478": {
            "question": "malo",
            "answer": "bad",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_479": {
            "question": "estabas",
            "answer": "You were",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_480": {
            "question": "vivo",
            "answer": "live",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_481": {
            "question": "haga",
            "answer": "make",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_482": {
            "question": "queda",
            "answer": "remains",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_483": {
            "question": "hijos",
            "answer": "sons",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_484": {
            "question": "mayor",
            "answer": "elderly",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_485": {
            "question": "fiesta",
            "answer": "party",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_486": {
            "question": "hacen",
            "answer": "make",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_487": {
            "question": "medio",
            "answer": "medium",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_488": {
            "question": "algunas",
            "answer": "some",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_489": {
            "question": "basta",
            "answer": "Enough",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_490": {
            "question": "arma",
            "answer": "weapon",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_491": {
            "question": "vino",
            "answer": "came",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_492": {
            "question": "meses",
            "answer": "months",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_493": {
            "question": "cuarto",
            "answer": "fourth",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_494": {
            "question": "\u00e9ste",
            "answer": "East",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_495": {
            "question": "escuela",
            "answer": "school",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_496": {
            "question": "est\u00e9",
            "answer": "East",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_497": {
            "question": "d\u00f3lares",
            "answer": "Dollars",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_498": {
            "question": "t\u00edo",
            "answer": "uncle",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_499": {
            "question": "posible",
            "answer": "possible",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_500": {
            "question": "tuve",
            "answer": "I had",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_501": {
            "question": "f\u00e1cil",
            "answer": "easy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_502": {
            "question": "preocupes",
            "answer": "worry",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_503": {
            "question": "luz",
            "answer": "light",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_504": {
            "question": "eran",
            "answer": "were",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_505": {
            "question": "carajo",
            "answer": "fuck",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_506": {
            "question": "final",
            "answer": "final",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_507": {
            "question": "lista",
            "answer": "ready",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_508": {
            "question": "trata",
            "answer": "about",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_509": {
            "question": "armas",
            "answer": "weapons",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_510": {
            "question": "hermana",
            "answer": "sister",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_511": {
            "question": "exactamente",
            "answer": "exactly",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_512": {
            "question": "chicas",
            "answer": "girls",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_513": {
            "question": "pod\u00eda",
            "answer": "could",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_514": {
            "question": "bastante",
            "answer": "Quite",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_515": {
            "question": "seguridad",
            "answer": "security",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_516": {
            "question": "pasando",
            "answer": "going",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_517": {
            "question": "esperando",
            "answer": "hoping for",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_518": {
            "question": "ac\u00e1",
            "answer": "here",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_519": {
            "question": "tel\u00e9fono",
            "answer": "telephone",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_520": {
            "question": "perro",
            "answer": "dog",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_521": {
            "question": "fuego",
            "answer": "fire",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_522": {
            "question": "muri\u00f3",
            "answer": "he died",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_523": {
            "question": "tampoco",
            "answer": "either",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_524": {
            "question": "sola",
            "answer": "alone",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_525": {
            "question": "estuvo",
            "answer": "he was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_526": {
            "question": "verte",
            "answer": "to see you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_527": {
            "question": "ir\u00e9",
            "answer": "I will go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_528": {
            "question": "tenido",
            "answer": "Dyed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_529": {
            "question": "culpa",
            "answer": "fault",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_530": {
            "question": "veras",
            "answer": "you'll see",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_531": {
            "question": "ad\u00f3nde",
            "answer": "where to",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_532": {
            "question": "buscando",
            "answer": "searching",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_533": {
            "question": "cuanto",
            "answer": "how much",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_534": {
            "question": "padres",
            "answer": "fathers",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_535": {
            "question": "paz",
            "answer": "peace",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_536": {
            "question": "demonios",
            "answer": "demons",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_537": {
            "question": "estar\u00e1",
            "answer": "will be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_538": {
            "question": "cual",
            "answer": "which",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_539": {
            "question": "perd\u00f3n",
            "answer": "sorry",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_540": {
            "question": "asi",
            "answer": "So",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_541": {
            "question": "jugar",
            "answer": "play",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_542": {
            "question": "pensando",
            "answer": "thinking",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_543": {
            "question": "esperar",
            "answer": "expect",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_544": {
            "question": "sabemos",
            "answer": "we know",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_545": {
            "question": "recuerdo",
            "answer": "memory",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_546": {
            "question": "par",
            "answer": "pair",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_547": {
            "question": "joven",
            "answer": "young man",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_548": {
            "question": "seguir",
            "answer": "continue",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_549": {
            "question": "pueblo",
            "answer": "village",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_550": {
            "question": "tenga",
            "answer": "have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_551": {
            "question": "caballeros",
            "answer": "gentlemen",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_552": {
            "question": "idiota",
            "answer": "moron",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_553": {
            "question": "dio",
            "answer": "it gave",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_554": {
            "question": "minuto",
            "answer": "minute",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_555": {
            "question": "beb\u00e9",
            "answer": "baby",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_556": {
            "question": "\u00fanica",
            "answer": "only",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_557": {
            "question": "lejos",
            "answer": "far",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_558": {
            "question": "nuestras",
            "answer": "ours",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_559": {
            "question": "plan",
            "answer": "plan",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_560": {
            "question": "pienso",
            "answer": "I think",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_561": {
            "question": "sentido",
            "answer": "sense",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_562": {
            "question": "dormir",
            "answer": "sleep",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_563": {
            "question": "digas",
            "answer": "you say",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_564": {
            "question": "palabra",
            "answer": "word",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_565": {
            "question": "correcto",
            "answer": "Right",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_566": {
            "question": "control",
            "answer": "control",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_567": {
            "question": "vemos",
            "answer": "we see",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_568": {
            "question": "entiendes",
            "answer": "You understand",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_569": {
            "question": "pa\u00eds",
            "answer": "country",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_570": {
            "question": "seis",
            "answer": "six",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_571": {
            "question": "\u00faltimo",
            "answer": "latest",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_572": {
            "question": "\u00e9sta",
            "answer": "is",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_573": {
            "question": "diga",
            "answer": "Say",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_574": {
            "question": "podr\u00edas",
            "answer": "could you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_575": {
            "question": "peque\u00f1a",
            "answer": "small",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_576": {
            "question": "c\u00e1llate",
            "answer": "shut",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_577": {
            "question": "trato",
            "answer": "deal",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_578": {
            "question": "rey",
            "answer": "king",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_579": {
            "question": "sucede",
            "answer": "happens",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_580": {
            "question": "muchachos",
            "answer": "boys",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_581": {
            "question": "jam\u00e1s",
            "answer": "Never",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_582": {
            "question": "cama",
            "answer": "bed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_583": {
            "question": "srta",
            "answer": "Ms",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_584": {
            "question": "ayudar",
            "answer": "help",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_585": {
            "question": "acerca",
            "answer": "about",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_586": {
            "question": "di",
            "answer": "gave",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_587": {
            "question": "cambio",
            "answer": "change",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_588": {
            "question": "falta",
            "answer": "lack",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_589": {
            "question": "hospital",
            "answer": "hospital",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_590": {
            "question": "lleva",
            "answer": "carries",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_591": {
            "question": "presidente",
            "answer": "President",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_592": {
            "question": "mil",
            "answer": "one thousand",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_593": {
            "question": "gusto",
            "answer": "taste",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_594": {
            "question": "conoces",
            "answer": "you know",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_595": {
            "question": "diciendo",
            "answer": "saying",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_596": {
            "question": "os",
            "answer": "you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_597": {
            "question": "ido",
            "answer": "gone",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_598": {
            "question": "general",
            "answer": "general",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_599": {
            "question": "extra\u00f1o",
            "answer": "weird",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_600": {
            "question": "semanas",
            "answer": "weeks",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_601": {
            "question": "coche",
            "answer": "car",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_602": {
            "question": "peor",
            "answer": "worse",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_603": {
            "question": "mucha",
            "answer": "a lot",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_604": {
            "question": "disculpe",
            "answer": "excuse me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_605": {
            "question": "dir\u00e9",
            "answer": "I'll say",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_606": {
            "question": "anoche",
            "answer": "last night",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_607": {
            "question": "perder",
            "answer": "lose",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_608": {
            "question": "v\u00e1monos",
            "answer": "Let's go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_609": {
            "question": "nave",
            "answer": "ship",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_610": {
            "question": "cielo",
            "answer": "darling",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_611": {
            "question": "habr\u00e1",
            "answer": "there will be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_612": {
            "question": "orden",
            "answer": "order",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_613": {
            "question": "segura",
            "answer": "safe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_614": {
            "question": "querida",
            "answer": "Dear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_615": {
            "question": "ni\u00f1a",
            "answer": "little girl",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_616": {
            "question": "incre\u00edble",
            "answer": "incredible",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_617": {
            "question": "adem\u00e1s",
            "answer": "what's more",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_618": {
            "question": "deben",
            "answer": "They must",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_619": {
            "question": "libro",
            "answer": "book",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_620": {
            "question": "calle",
            "answer": "street",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_621": {
            "question": "caf\u00e9",
            "answer": "coffee",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_622": {
            "question": "piensas",
            "answer": "You think",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_623": {
            "question": "hacemos",
            "answer": "we make",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_624": {
            "question": "especial",
            "answer": "special",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_625": {
            "question": "queremos",
            "answer": "we want",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_626": {
            "question": "irme",
            "answer": "Go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_627": {
            "question": "perfecto",
            "answer": "perfect",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_628": {
            "question": "buscar",
            "answer": "Search",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_629": {
            "question": "odio",
            "answer": "hatred",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_630": {
            "question": "piensa",
            "answer": "think",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_631": {
            "question": "oficina",
            "answer": "office",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_632": {
            "question": "hablas",
            "answer": "speak",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_633": {
            "question": "libre",
            "answer": "free",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_634": {
            "question": "agente",
            "answer": "agent",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_635": {
            "question": "york",
            "answer": "York",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_636": {
            "question": "llamar",
            "answer": "to call",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_637": {
            "question": "mala",
            "answer": "bad",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_638": {
            "question": "detr\u00e1s",
            "answer": "behind",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_639": {
            "question": "viste",
            "answer": "dresses",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_640": {
            "question": "dile",
            "answer": "tell him",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_641": {
            "question": "grandes",
            "answer": "large",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_642": {
            "question": "recuerdas",
            "answer": "remember",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_643": {
            "question": "real",
            "answer": "real",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_644": {
            "question": "estaban",
            "answer": "They were",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_645": {
            "question": "m\u00eda",
            "answer": "mine",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_646": {
            "question": "frente",
            "answer": "front",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_647": {
            "question": "perdido",
            "answer": "lost",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_648": {
            "question": "llamo",
            "answer": "called",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_649": {
            "question": "muertos",
            "answer": "dead",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_650": {
            "question": "millones",
            "answer": "millions",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_651": {
            "question": "asesino",
            "answer": "assassin",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_652": {
            "question": "sue\u00f1o",
            "answer": "sleep",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_653": {
            "question": "quisiera",
            "answer": "I would like",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_654": {
            "question": "habr\u00eda",
            "answer": "there would be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_655": {
            "question": "har\u00e1",
            "answer": "will do",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_656": {
            "question": "viaje",
            "answer": "trip",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_657": {
            "question": "probablemente",
            "answer": "probably",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_658": {
            "question": "resto",
            "answer": "rest",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_659": {
            "question": "estar\u00e9",
            "answer": "I will be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_660": {
            "question": "maldici\u00f3n",
            "answer": "damn",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_661": {
            "question": "lamento",
            "answer": "lament",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_662": {
            "question": "muchacho",
            "answer": "young guy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_663": {
            "question": "avi\u00f3n",
            "answer": "airplane",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_664": {
            "question": "ropa",
            "answer": "clothing",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_665": {
            "question": "fuerza",
            "answer": "strength",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_666": {
            "question": "llamado",
            "answer": "called",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_667": {
            "question": "o\u00eddo",
            "answer": "ear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_668": {
            "question": "dado",
            "answer": "given",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_669": {
            "question": "encima",
            "answer": "over",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_670": {
            "question": "negro",
            "answer": "black",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_671": {
            "question": "usar",
            "answer": "use",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_672": {
            "question": "informaci\u00f3n",
            "answer": "information",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_673": {
            "question": "uds",
            "answer": "You",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_674": {
            "question": "preguntas",
            "answer": "questions",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_675": {
            "question": "tuvo",
            "answer": "He had",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_676": {
            "question": "secreto",
            "answer": "secret",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_677": {
            "question": "vuelve",
            "answer": "Come back",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_678": {
            "question": "miren",
            "answer": "Look",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_679": {
            "question": "quieras",
            "answer": "You want",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_680": {
            "question": "har\u00eda",
            "answer": "would do",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_681": {
            "question": "acaba",
            "answer": "just",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_682": {
            "question": "otras",
            "answer": "others",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_683": {
            "question": "incluso",
            "answer": "even",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_684": {
            "question": "sientes",
            "answer": "you feel",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_685": {
            "question": "deber\u00edamos",
            "answer": "we should",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_686": {
            "question": "haz",
            "answer": "make",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_687": {
            "question": "decirte",
            "answer": "tell you",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_688": {
            "question": "boca",
            "answer": "mouth",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_689": {
            "question": "dolor",
            "answer": "pain",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_690": {
            "question": "ba\u00f1o",
            "answer": "bath",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_691": {
            "question": "adentro",
            "answer": "indoors",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_692": {
            "question": "profesor",
            "answer": "professor",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_693": {
            "question": "habitaci\u00f3n",
            "answer": "room",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_694": {
            "question": "da\u00f1o",
            "answer": "damage",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_695": {
            "question": "tuyo",
            "answer": "yours",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_696": {
            "question": "seas",
            "answer": "You are",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_697": {
            "question": "noticias",
            "answer": "news",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_698": {
            "question": "dem\u00e1s",
            "answer": "the rest",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_699": {
            "question": "querido",
            "answer": "Dear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_700": {
            "question": "duro",
            "answer": "Lasted",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_701": {
            "question": "poner",
            "answer": "put",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_702": {
            "question": "prueba",
            "answer": "Test",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_703": {
            "question": "mire",
            "answer": "Look",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_704": {
            "question": "tonto",
            "answer": "fool",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_705": {
            "question": "campo",
            "answer": "countryside",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_706": {
            "question": "siendo",
            "answer": "being",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_707": {
            "question": "diez",
            "answer": "ten",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_708": {
            "question": "\u00e9se",
            "answer": "that",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_709": {
            "question": "tranquilo",
            "answer": "calm",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_710": {
            "question": "asunto",
            "answer": "affair",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_711": {
            "question": "acab\u00f3",
            "answer": "just",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_712": {
            "question": "qu\u00e9date",
            "answer": "stay",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_713": {
            "question": "derecho",
            "answer": "law",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_714": {
            "question": "placer",
            "answer": "pleasure",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_715": {
            "question": "recuerda",
            "answer": "remember",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_716": {
            "question": "estuve",
            "answer": "was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_717": {
            "question": "tratando",
            "answer": "trying",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_718": {
            "question": "ej\u00e9rcito",
            "answer": "army",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_719": {
            "question": "futuro",
            "answer": "future",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_720": {
            "question": "llevar",
            "answer": "wear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_721": {
            "question": "compa\u00f1\u00eda",
            "answer": "company",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_722": {
            "question": "venido",
            "answer": "I come",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_723": {
            "question": "listos",
            "answer": "Ready",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_724": {
            "question": "haremos",
            "answer": "will",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_725": {
            "question": "sitio",
            "answer": "place",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_726": {
            "question": "verlo",
            "answer": "see him",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_727": {
            "question": "puesto",
            "answer": "Market Stall",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_728": {
            "question": "atenci\u00f3n",
            "answer": "attention",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_729": {
            "question": "sino",
            "answer": "otherwise",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_730": {
            "question": "cambiar",
            "answer": "change",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_731": {
            "question": "error",
            "answer": "mistake",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_732": {
            "question": "blanco",
            "answer": "white",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_733": {
            "question": "raro",
            "answer": "rare",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_734": {
            "question": "palabras",
            "answer": "words",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_735": {
            "question": "lleg\u00f3",
            "answer": "I arrive",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_736": {
            "question": "sal",
            "answer": "Salt",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_737": {
            "question": "pase",
            "answer": "happens",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_738": {
            "question": "mente",
            "answer": "mind",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_739": {
            "question": "sistema",
            "answer": "system",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_740": {
            "question": "pel\u00edcula",
            "answer": "movie",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_741": {
            "question": "anda",
            "answer": "walk",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_742": {
            "question": "ello",
            "answer": "it",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_743": {
            "question": "negocio",
            "answer": "business",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_744": {
            "question": "novia",
            "answer": "girlfriend",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_745": {
            "question": "permiso",
            "answer": "permission",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_746": {
            "question": "cre\u00ed",
            "answer": "I believed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_747": {
            "question": "suena",
            "answer": "sounds",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_748": {
            "question": "ocurre",
            "answer": "occurs",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_749": {
            "question": "oficial",
            "answer": "official",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_750": {
            "question": "espere",
            "answer": "Wait",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_751": {
            "question": "aire",
            "answer": "air",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_752": {
            "question": "mat\u00f3",
            "answer": "killed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_753": {
            "question": "regresar",
            "answer": "to return",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_754": {
            "question": "vio",
            "answer": "he saw",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_755": {
            "question": "hazlo",
            "answer": "do it",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_756": {
            "question": "trasero",
            "answer": "rear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_757": {
            "question": "grupo",
            "answer": "cluster",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_758": {
            "question": "entendido",
            "answer": "it is understood",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_759": {
            "question": "se\u00f1orita",
            "answer": "Miss",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_760": {
            "question": "m\u00fasica",
            "answer": "music",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_761": {
            "question": "perra",
            "answer": "bitch",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_762": {
            "question": "conoce",
            "answer": "known",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_763": {
            "question": "empezar",
            "answer": "start",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_764": {
            "question": "siente",
            "answer": "Feel",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_765": {
            "question": "acabo",
            "answer": "I finish",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_766": {
            "question": "est\u00fapido",
            "answer": "idiot",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_767": {
            "question": "diferente",
            "answer": "different",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_768": {
            "question": "traje",
            "answer": "costume",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_769": {
            "question": "modo",
            "answer": "mode",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_770": {
            "question": "encontr\u00e9",
            "answer": "I found",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_771": {
            "question": "mensaje",
            "answer": "message",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_772": {
            "question": "llamada",
            "answer": "call",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_773": {
            "question": "navidad",
            "answer": "Christmas",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_774": {
            "question": "eras",
            "answer": "ages",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_775": {
            "question": "pena",
            "answer": "grief",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_776": {
            "question": "largo",
            "answer": "length",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_777": {
            "question": "entra",
            "answer": "enters",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_778": {
            "question": "piso",
            "answer": "flat",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_779": {
            "question": "foto",
            "answer": "Photo",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_780": {
            "question": "dijeron",
            "answer": "They said",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_781": {
            "question": "m\u00e9dico",
            "answer": "medical",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_782": {
            "question": "accidente",
            "answer": "accident",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_783": {
            "question": "fuiste",
            "answer": "you were",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_784": {
            "question": "imposible",
            "answer": "impossible",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_785": {
            "question": "podr\u00edamos",
            "answer": "we could",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_786": {
            "question": "l\u00ednea",
            "answer": "line",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_787": {
            "question": "propia",
            "answer": "own",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_788": {
            "question": "barco",
            "answer": "boat",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_789": {
            "question": "ganar",
            "answer": "gain",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_790": {
            "question": "normal",
            "answer": "normal",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_791": {
            "question": "segundos",
            "answer": "seconds",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_792": {
            "question": "vive",
            "answer": "it lives",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_793": {
            "question": "mitad",
            "answer": "half",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_794": {
            "question": "quiera",
            "answer": "want",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_795": {
            "question": "tras",
            "answer": "after",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_796": {
            "question": "decirle",
            "answer": "Tell him",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_797": {
            "question": "lindo",
            "answer": "pretty",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_798": {
            "question": "funciona",
            "answer": "works",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_799": {
            "question": "programa",
            "answer": "Program",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_800": {
            "question": "vine",
            "answer": "came",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_801": {
            "question": "abre",
            "answer": "opens",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_802": {
            "question": "sean",
            "answer": "Sean",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_803": {
            "question": "pagar",
            "answer": "to pay",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_804": {
            "question": "fotos",
            "answer": "Photos",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_805": {
            "question": "centro",
            "answer": "center",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_806": {
            "question": "supone",
            "answer": "It supposes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_807": {
            "question": "basura",
            "answer": "trash",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_808": {
            "question": "situaci\u00f3n",
            "answer": "situation",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_809": {
            "question": "mejores",
            "answer": "top",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_810": {
            "question": "vienen",
            "answer": "they come",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_811": {
            "question": "encanta",
            "answer": "loves",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_812": {
            "question": "marido",
            "answer": "husband",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_813": {
            "question": "personal",
            "answer": "staff",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_814": {
            "question": "maestro",
            "answer": "teacher",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_815": {
            "question": "hambre",
            "answer": "hunger",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_816": {
            "question": "ataque",
            "answer": "attack",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_817": {
            "question": "culo",
            "answer": "ass",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_818": {
            "question": "dale",
            "answer": "Go ahead",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_819": {
            "question": "pie",
            "answer": "foot",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_820": {
            "question": "conseguir",
            "answer": "get",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_821": {
            "question": "trabajando",
            "answer": "working",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_822": {
            "question": "gracioso",
            "answer": "funny",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_823": {
            "question": "dej\u00f3",
            "answer": "let",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_824": {
            "question": "pudo",
            "answer": "could",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_825": {
            "question": "derecha",
            "answer": "right",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_826": {
            "question": "izquierda",
            "answer": "left",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_827": {
            "question": "pr\u00f3xima",
            "answer": "next",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_828": {
            "question": "pobre",
            "answer": "poor",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_829": {
            "question": "respuesta",
            "answer": "response",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_830": {
            "question": "tipos",
            "answer": "types",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_831": {
            "question": "sentir",
            "answer": "feel",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_832": {
            "question": "ten\u00edas",
            "answer": "You had",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_833": {
            "question": "pude",
            "answer": "I could",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_834": {
            "question": "darle",
            "answer": "give him",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_835": {
            "question": "voz",
            "answer": "voice",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_836": {
            "question": "amiga",
            "answer": "friend",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_837": {
            "question": "gustan",
            "answer": "like",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_838": {
            "question": "vista",
            "answer": "view",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_839": {
            "question": "salvo",
            "answer": "except",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_840": {
            "question": "loca",
            "answer": "crazy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_841": {
            "question": "hotel",
            "answer": "hotel",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_842": {
            "question": "hicieron",
            "answer": "they made",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_843": {
            "question": "ten",
            "answer": "Ten",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_844": {
            "question": "temo",
            "answer": "I fear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_845": {
            "question": "se\u00f1al",
            "answer": "sign",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_846": {
            "question": "pelo",
            "answer": "hair",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_847": {
            "question": "llevo",
            "answer": "wear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_848": {
            "question": "ayer",
            "answer": "Yesterday",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_849": {
            "question": "das",
            "answer": "you give",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_850": {
            "question": "nena",
            "answer": "chick",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_851": {
            "question": "servicio",
            "answer": "service",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_852": {
            "question": "tren",
            "answer": "train",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_853": {
            "question": "bonito",
            "answer": "nice",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_854": {
            "question": "mes",
            "answer": "month",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_855": {
            "question": "tendr\u00e1",
            "answer": "will have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_856": {
            "question": "tendr\u00e1s",
            "answer": "you will have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_857": {
            "question": "edad",
            "answer": "age",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_858": {
            "question": "ellas",
            "answer": "they",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_859": {
            "question": "hermosa",
            "answer": "beautifull",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_860": {
            "question": "honor",
            "answer": "honor",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_861": {
            "question": "simplemente",
            "answer": "simply",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_862": {
            "question": "llamas",
            "answer": "calls",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_863": {
            "question": "tengas",
            "answer": "Have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_864": {
            "question": "corre",
            "answer": "runs",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_865": {
            "question": "baja",
            "answer": "short",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_866": {
            "question": "sol",
            "answer": "sun",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_867": {
            "question": "si\u00e9ntate",
            "answer": "Sit down",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_868": {
            "question": "dan",
            "answer": "give",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_869": {
            "question": "humano",
            "answer": "human",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_870": {
            "question": "divertido",
            "answer": "funny",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_871": {
            "question": "sexo",
            "answer": "sex",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_872": {
            "question": "vuelto",
            "answer": "turned",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_873": {
            "question": "peligro",
            "answer": "danger",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_874": {
            "question": "mesa",
            "answer": "table",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_875": {
            "question": "siguiente",
            "answer": "Next",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_876": {
            "question": "hablo",
            "answer": "talked",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_877": {
            "question": "disculpa",
            "answer": "Sorry",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_878": {
            "question": "decirme",
            "answer": "Tell me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_879": {
            "question": "caja",
            "answer": "cash register",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_880": {
            "question": "negocios",
            "answer": "business",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_881": {
            "question": "misi\u00f3n",
            "answer": "mission",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_882": {
            "question": "silencio",
            "answer": "silence",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_883": {
            "question": "sale",
            "answer": "comes out",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_884": {
            "question": "llegado",
            "answer": "arrived",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_885": {
            "question": "estar\u00eda",
            "answer": "It would",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_886": {
            "question": "regreso",
            "answer": "Return",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_887": {
            "question": "media",
            "answer": "half",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_888": {
            "question": "estan",
            "answer": "are",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_889": {
            "question": "propio",
            "answer": "own self",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_890": {
            "question": "oro",
            "answer": "Prayed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_891": {
            "question": "enseguida",
            "answer": "right away",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_892": {
            "question": "linda",
            "answer": "pretty",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_893": {
            "question": "prometo",
            "answer": "I promise",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_894": {
            "question": "esposo",
            "answer": "husband",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_895": {
            "question": "norte",
            "answer": "north",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_896": {
            "question": "hubo",
            "answer": "there was",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_897": {
            "question": "juro",
            "answer": "I swear",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_898": {
            "question": "muerta",
            "answer": "dead",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_899": {
            "question": "interesante",
            "answer": "interesting",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_900": {
            "question": "pensaba",
            "answer": "thought",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_901": {
            "question": "busca",
            "answer": "search",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_902": {
            "question": "terminar",
            "answer": "end up",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_903": {
            "question": "tendr\u00e9",
            "answer": "I will have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_904": {
            "question": "completamente",
            "answer": "completely",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_905": {
            "question": "cita",
            "answer": "date",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_906": {
            "question": "siete",
            "answer": "seven",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_907": {
            "question": "cumplea\u00f1os",
            "answer": "birthday",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_908": {
            "question": "abogado",
            "answer": "attorney",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_909": {
            "question": "alrededor",
            "answer": "around",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_910": {
            "question": "cerebro",
            "answer": "brain",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_911": {
            "question": "porqu\u00e9",
            "answer": "because",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_912": {
            "question": "llave",
            "answer": "wrench",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_913": {
            "question": "santo",
            "answer": "holy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_914": {
            "question": "hermoso",
            "answer": "handsome",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_915": {
            "question": "necesario",
            "answer": "necessary",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_916": {
            "question": "edificio",
            "answer": "building",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_917": {
            "question": "irnos",
            "answer": "Go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_918": {
            "question": "aun",
            "answer": "still",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_919": {
            "question": "tendremos",
            "answer": "we will have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_920": {
            "question": "vayas",
            "answer": "go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_921": {
            "question": "doy",
            "answer": "give",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_922": {
            "question": "trae",
            "answer": "Bring",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_923": {
            "question": "sali\u00f3",
            "answer": "he left",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_924": {
            "question": "ley",
            "answer": "law",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_925": {
            "question": "ahi",
            "answer": "over there",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_926": {
            "question": "verdadero",
            "answer": "real",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_927": {
            "question": "pelea",
            "answer": "Fight",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_928": {
            "question": "banco",
            "answer": "bank",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_929": {
            "question": "terrible",
            "answer": "terrible",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_930": {
            "question": "calma",
            "answer": "Calm down",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_931": {
            "question": "cena",
            "answer": "Dinner",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_932": {
            "question": "dar\u00e9",
            "answer": "I will give",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_933": {
            "question": "gobierno",
            "answer": "government",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_934": {
            "question": "comprar",
            "answer": "to buy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_935": {
            "question": "creen",
            "answer": "They believe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_936": {
            "question": "sargento",
            "answer": "sergeant",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_937": {
            "question": "destino",
            "answer": "destiny",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_938": {
            "question": "existe",
            "answer": "exists",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_939": {
            "question": "hac\u00eda",
            "answer": "towards",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_940": {
            "question": "novio",
            "answer": "boyfriend",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_941": {
            "question": "sala",
            "answer": "living room",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_942": {
            "question": "trav\u00e9s",
            "answer": "through",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_943": {
            "question": "regalo",
            "answer": "gift",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_944": {
            "question": "iglesia",
            "answer": "church",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_945": {
            "question": "dec\u00eda",
            "answer": "He said",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_946": {
            "question": "cualquiera",
            "answer": "any",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_947": {
            "question": "excelente",
            "answer": "Excellent",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_948": {
            "question": "esperen",
            "answer": "Wait",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_949": {
            "question": "deseo",
            "answer": "desire",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_950": {
            "question": "alma",
            "answer": "soul",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_951": {
            "question": "diablo",
            "answer": "Devil",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_952": {
            "question": "deje",
            "answer": "leave",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_953": {
            "question": "cu\u00e1ntos",
            "answer": "many",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_954": {
            "question": "espada",
            "answer": "sword",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_955": {
            "question": "est\u00e1bamos",
            "answer": "We were",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_956": {
            "question": "carne",
            "answer": "meat",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_957": {
            "question": "maravilloso",
            "answer": "wonderful",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_958": {
            "question": "vidas",
            "answer": "lives",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_959": {
            "question": "sucedi\u00f3",
            "answer": "happened",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_960": {
            "question": "o\u00ed",
            "answer": "I heard",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_961": {
            "question": "peligroso",
            "answer": "dangerous",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_962": {
            "question": "direcci\u00f3n",
            "answer": "address",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_963": {
            "question": "libertad",
            "answer": "freedom",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_964": {
            "question": "jes\u00fas",
            "answer": "Jesus",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_965": {
            "question": "ocurri\u00f3",
            "answer": "It occurred",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_966": {
            "question": "ver\u00e9",
            "answer": "I will see",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_967": {
            "question": "sue\u00f1os",
            "answer": "dreams",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_968": {
            "question": "pudiera",
            "answer": "could",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_969": {
            "question": "detective",
            "answer": "detective",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_970": {
            "question": "sorpresa",
            "answer": "surprise",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_971": {
            "question": "tuya",
            "answer": "yours",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_972": {
            "question": "pies",
            "answer": "feet",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_973": {
            "question": "club",
            "answer": "club",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_974": {
            "question": "terminado",
            "answer": "finished",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_975": {
            "question": "infierno",
            "answer": "hell",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_976": {
            "question": "cre\u00eda",
            "answer": "I believed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_977": {
            "question": "luna",
            "answer": "Moon",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_978": {
            "question": "salvar",
            "answer": "save",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_979": {
            "question": "carta",
            "answer": "letter",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_980": {
            "question": "est\u00e9s",
            "answer": "be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_981": {
            "question": "cielos",
            "answer": "Heavens",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_982": {
            "question": "teniente",
            "answer": "lieutenant",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_983": {
            "question": "encuentra",
            "answer": "find",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_984": {
            "question": "veamos",
            "answer": "let's see",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_985": {
            "question": "quise",
            "answer": "I wanted",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_986": {
            "question": "esc\u00fachame",
            "answer": "listen to me",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_987": {
            "question": "necesitan",
            "answer": "They need",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_988": {
            "question": "ambos",
            "answer": "both of them",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_989": {
            "question": "decisi\u00f3n",
            "answer": "decision",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_990": {
            "question": "enemigo",
            "answer": "enemy",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_991": {
            "question": "hicimos",
            "answer": "we did",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_992": {
            "question": "dulce",
            "answer": "sweet",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_993": {
            "question": "pruebas",
            "answer": "tests",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_994": {
            "question": "quer\u00edas",
            "answer": "You wanted",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_995": {
            "question": "abuelo",
            "answer": "grandfather",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_996": {
            "question": "totalmente",
            "answer": "totally",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_997": {
            "question": "mirando",
            "answer": "looking at",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_998": {
            "question": "vayan",
            "answer": "go",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_999": {
            "question": "carrera",
            "answer": "race",
            "know_it": 0
        }
    }
}